<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Excel</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_nd">CompetitionNDActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info_nd">Info</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_alarm_receiver">AlarmReceiverActivity</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_meal_list">MealSpotting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_meal">NewMealActivity</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_new">Add a Meal</string>
    <string name="meal_label">Add a Meal</string>
    <string name="save_button_text">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel_button_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first_runactivity">FirstRunactivity</string>
    <string name="clickhere">Already Registered? <u>Click Here</u> </string>
    <string name="hashincl_rules">• This is strictly an individual online event.• The duration of the event is 5 days (7200 minutes)\n• Registration is required for participation and there should be no duplicate accounts.\n• Coding should be in C. No other language will be accepted.\n• There will be a total of 30 questions.\n• Questions will be of three types and scoring pattern is as follows:\n1. Easy - 5 points    2. Medium - 7 points    3. Hard - 10 points\n• The program submitted by the participant will be considered correct if it gives the expected output for all the test cases.\n• Participants can compile and test the code before submitting. If it shows “All sample test cases passed” during testing and still shows “Wrong Answer” after submission, it is a presentation error. It can be avoided by properly formatting the output.\n• The ranking is done as follows:\no The one with the highest score is ranked first.\no In case if 2 or more persons have the same score, then they are ranked by the least total time taken to solve all the problems.\no The total time is the sum of the time consumed for each problem solved. The time consumed for a solved problem is the time elapsed from the beginning of the contest to the submittal of the accepted run plus 20 minutes for each rejected run. There is no time consumed for a problem that is not solved.\n• A live points table will be maintained so that the participant can check his/her ranking.\n• If any malicious activity like submitting the duplicate code is detected the user account will be deleted without prior notice.\n• Rules are subject to change at any point in time.• If any malicious activity like submitting the duplicate code is detected the user account will be deleted without prior notice.\n\n</string>
    <string name="loc_intro">“Talk is cheap, show me the code ” – Linus Torvalds .\nAre you ready to manipulate lines of code to outwit and outshine your opponents and rise as the one true Lord of the Code?</string>

</resources>
